As we witness the advancement of forces of wickedness further into Palestine to continue to commit acts that are governed by a body that we know is not of the spirit or of the soul, it makes for many of us a feeling of hopelessness.
And though I am not a religious person, I do connect with the spirit and I am a believer that we as a unit are the spirit and we can make change.
And so I invite you to raise your voices and read with me this prayer posted by the brilliant Orson Shire.
Bismillah ar-Rahman ar-Rahim. In the name of Allah, the most gracious, the most merciful.
Ya Allah, the sustainer of all worlds, we turn to you in desperate plea for the Palestinian people.
Protect them from the bombardment they face.
Shield them from the siege and save them from the hands that aim to harm them.
Ya Rahman, mend the broken hearts of those who have lost their homes, family and hope.
Strengthen their Iman in times of despair and grant them unwavering saber in their struggles.
Raise their ranks among the righteous and the martyrs in the hereafter.
Ya Mu'iz, empower them with resilience and fortitude.
Grant them the victory that you promised to the oppressed and let them reclaim their rights and their lands.
Ya Ar-Rahman ar-Rahman, shower them with your infinite mercy.
Comfort the grieving mother, the frightened child, the desperate father and every soul in pain.
Let their tears be a testament to their patience and their unwavering faith in you.
Ya Jabbar, mend their communities, heal their wounds and fortify their spirits.
Bestow upon them the means to rebuild, making them stronger than before.
Ya Allah, hasten the day of their liberation, where peace and justice reign and where they can live in their lands freely and without fear.
Grant them justice against their oppressors and let those who inflict harm upon them be humiliated in this world and the next.
Amin.